A production line stops.
In seconds, a perfect plan becomes impossible.
CableTwin is a living digital twin that lets the manager see before deciding.
This is the live factory twin: three cable lines, ten client orders, streaming simulated sensors - speed, temperature, tension, power.
Fully synthetic data, running locally, completely offline.
At ten o'clock, Line 2 stops for four hours.
Watch the engine explore seventeen thousand eight hundred fifty-six candidate schedules and keep the ten thousand four hundred forty feasible ones - live, in front of you.
A local machine-learning model, trained on six hundred eighty-seven incidents simulated by the twin itself, recommends the balanced Cost route at seventy-nine percent confidence.
Line two's telemetry flatlines;
plant power drops in real time.
The manager stays in command and chooses Service instead: priority orders glide to lines one and three, crews are mobilized, and projected delay falls from six hundred twenty to one hundred forty minutes.
One click approves the plan.
Nothing is ever sent to a machine - the decision lands in an audit trail: who decided, when, on which numbers.
Behind the twin, the same deterministic engine powers the full decision view - revised Gantt, before-and-after KPIs, complete traceability.
Verified by nine automated checks, an exact exhaustive benchmark, and a dedicated five-test harness for the recommender.
Scan the link - it runs live in your browser.