A production line stops.
In seconds, a plan that looked perfect becomes impossible.
CableTwin helps the manager see before deciding.
This is a fully synthetic Tunisian cable-factory scenario: three lines, ten orders, all planned on time.
The prototype runs locally, offline, without a cloud service.
At 10:00, Line 2 stops for four hours.
Without rescheduling, three orders are exposed, only seven stay on time, and projected cumulative delay reaches 620 minutes.
CableTwin does not hide one answer.
Its symbolic, constraint-based planner builds three feasible routes from the same data.
Service protects priority-weighted deadlines;
Cost minimizes the illustrative comparison cost;
Stability avoids line reassignments.
Every route respects eligibility, duration, downtime, non-overlap and the planning horizon.
Before acting, the manager previews the revised Gantt and compares consequences.
Service cuts projected delay from 620 to 140 minutes, reduces overtime from 180 to 30 minutes, and reaches 216 kilometres by 18:00 versus 188.
Cost uses two line changes instead of three and has the lowest synthetic cost.
Nothing is sent to a machine.
The production manager selects a route, approves it, and CableTwin records who decided, when, and which metrics supported the choice.
This working prototype is verified by nine tests and an independent exhaustive check of 17,856 candidate schedules.
Next: a read-only shadow pilot on historical incidents.